

Chase Lindsay

PRODUCT MANAGER & SOFTWARE ENGINEER

About

My mission is to positively impact the world through code. I strive to continuously improve myself and the lives of others around me. I worked in NYC as an adtech analyst for three years and subsequently explored the world. I have traveled to more than 35 countries and have learned about many different cultures and ways of life. Along the way, I discovered my passion for programming and decided to attend a software engineering bootcamp. After the bootcamp, I became a product manager in NYC. I led a team of developers and worked with them daily, which reignited my passion for coding.

Skills

Project Management

Problem Solving

Ruby on Rails

React

chase.lindsay1@gmail.com



in bit.ly/3hPTZo9

Work Experience

TransPerfect Translation | NY, NY Aug 2020 - Aug 2021

Product Manager

- Oversaw development of project management tool to host 300K+ translation projects with integrations to other enterprise-level applications.
- Increased communication, removed bottlenecks, and pushed multiple builds per day by leveraging continuous integration model and continuous feedback.
- Defined and prioritized the product roadmap that meets user needs and corporate goals
- Fostered collaboration between engineers, UX, quality assurance, and marketing teams to meet product targets.

Involved Media | NY, NY

Nov 2016 - Jan 2018

Programmatic Buyer / Account Manager

- Owned daily operation and mastered trading-related technologies, including DSPs, DMP, 3rd party ad servers and manual exchanges
- Actively optimized and managed client campaigns including: strategy development, project management, and optimization log upkeep
- Leveraged and improved established processes, documents, checklists, etc. that ensured efficient procedures and continual improvement for both new and existing clients.
- Communicated with partners (technology, media, and data) to oversee the launch and ongoing execution of campaigns

Triad Retail Media

Sept 2015 - Nov 2016

Programmatic Buyer

- Launched and optimized programmatic campaigns for national retailers such as Colgate and Coca Cola
- Conducted in-depth data analysis to identify key trends that impact campaign performance
- Maintained a close relationship with account managers to ensure campaigns were properly executed and met performance goals

Education History

Le Wagon Engineering Bootcamp

Full Stack Development Jan 2020 - March 2020

University of North Georgia

BBA of Finance Aug 2010 - Dec 2014